Do I look fat?
I'm serious.
Do I?
Yes.Yes, you look fat.
As big as a house.
I cannot believe youjust said that.
And here I am,carrying your baby.
How do I know it's my baby?
Do you know whatyour problem is?
You've got a chip onyour shoulder.
Yes.
Just can't.
And it's as big as a boulder.
I can't take it. I can'ttake it, excuse me.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Sir, are you okay?
Is thereanything you need?
Yes.I need a musical.
A BIG
GAY
MUSICAL!
I love being OFF Broadway!
Ladies and gentleman,
welcome to the first previewof "Adam and Steve -
Just the Way God Made ‘Em."
Before the show begins,
we need to let you know thatthe show was rated "FLAMING
by the Coalition of Christians.
But that doesn't mean it'sabout homosexuals.
It just means, that ifyou enjoy this show,
you'll end up burning inhell, right next to us.
[Applause]
Hi! I'm Adam.
And I'm his husband, Steven.
And this is our story.
In the beginning,
God created the Heavensand the Earth.
Wait a minute!
That's not howit's supposed to begin.You grabbed the wrong book.
Sorry.
In the beginning,
God was... bored.
He was all alonein the universe,
and the thought of being aloneforever bothered Him.
He realized what he neededwere beautiful beingsto entertain Him.
So, God created the angels.
And they were hot.
Each angel was hotand sexy
and male.
God loved the angels,
but soon realizedthat He wanted more.
So, God created the Earth.
♪ He made the Earth full of beauty and wonder. ♪
♪ He made the sky full of stars like no one could. ♪
♪ He made the oceans and rivers and mountains. ♪
♪ And He knew ♪
♪ it was good. ♪
♪ One day God came down to Earth and summoned all His might. ♪
♪ He took one look at the darkness and said ♪
Why the fuck is itso dark down here?
Oh, that's better.
Aren't they great?
Let's show ‘em angels!
♪ It's God. He's the one creator. ♪
♪ It's God. He's the entertainer. ♪
♪ It's God. He's the great orator. ♪
♪ It's God. He's the mastur... ♪
[Gasp]
What?He is the master.
♪ I am God. ♪
♪ I created the plants and the trees. ♪
♪ I made all the animals - the birds and the bees. ♪
♪ I made everything that you see, ♪
♪ but none of it satisfied me. ♪
♪ I needed interaction and drama. ♪
♪ I needed something entertaining to see. ♪
♪ I loved all the stuff that I created, ♪
♪ but it's like a nature show on TV. ♪
So God created a man.
Adam was just what God wanted.
A man to do the gardening,
take care of the animals.
But, Adam was lonely.
And, God wasn't very fondof what Adam was doingwith the animals.
[Baa...]
So God created Eve,a woman for Adam.
And they were happy.
For a while.
You couldn't even makeme something to eat?
Don't you start with me!
But the shit hit the fan whenthey ate God's favorite fruit.
Here!Eat this.
[THUNDER]
Jesus Christ!
Yes daddy?
Nothing.Go back to bed.
It wasn't my fault.I swear.
It was a serpent.
Yeah, a serpent.
♪ And so I threw them both out of my garden. ♪
♪ What else was there for me to do? ♪
♪ But then the garden just seemed so empty, ♪
♪ and I was depressed and I was so blue. ♪
Hey God. Why don'tyou try two men?
What the hell!Let's try it!
♪ I made another Adam for my garden, ♪
♪ but I didn't make another Eve. ♪
♪ I made another man a bit more sensitive, ♪
♪ and I called him Steve! ♪
♪ And that is how it all began, ♪
♪ the story of Adam and Steve. ♪
♪ Though it's not written in the Bible, ♪
♪ it's the truth from above so believe. ♪
♪ And now here's Adam and Steve. ♪
♪ God bless Adam and Steve. ♪
Just the way I made 'em!
Really good show guys.
Yeah, for a first preview, itwas actually pretty good.
Where are you rushing off to?
-I don't do stage doors.-What do you mean?
There's nothing I hate morethan people at the stage door.
They feel like they have totell you how good you are.
It's fake and awkwardand I just don't do it.
Oh look, Patti LuPone.
Do you always beatthe audience?
So far so good.
What about your fans?
My "fans ?Yeah right.
Oh, I'm working at MostlySondheim later,
so if you wanna stopby, let me know.
I cant wait to hear some fatguy singing "All that Jazz.
Or some flamer singing "AndI am telling you, Sophie."
Show tunes and booze kids.That's what keeps me happy.
-I'll see you guys later.-Yeah later.
Oh, I'm sorry!
No problem.See you tomorrow.
Hey babe.Great first preview.
See you soon.Smiley face.
We are so proud of you.
You're gonna be such a big star in New York City.
It's just Off-Broadway.
Just Off-Broadway?
People would sell their souls
to be starring in anOff-Broadway show,and don't you forget it.
We just wanted to call and tellyou how proud we are of you.
And congratulations.
Thank you.
We have a surprise for you.
We're coming to youropening night.
Hey, we weren't going tomiss your big night, huh?
Hey, we've been toall the others.
How could we miss your firstNew York City opening night?
The first of many.
Oh, great!
Hey, we should let yougo and enjoy your success.
Oh yeah, God bless.
We love you honey.
God bless.
I love you too.
Hi everyone. Welcometo Mostly Sondheim!
We have one hellof a crowd here.
Mostly Sondheim is like an openmic night for show tunes.
Every song you sing hasto be from a show
or from a songwriter thathas written a show.
Oh, actually you cansing whatever you want
if you tip twenty dollars.We don't care.
And I couldn't imaginebeginning Mostly Sondheim
without hearing mygorgeous co-host,
Kate Pazakis' gregarious,fabulous vocal chords.
Gregarious?
I don't know. I justmade up the word.
So, hit it Jack! Anddon't forget to tip.
♪ Friday night. ♪
♪ I spend the whole week waiting for Friday night. ♪
♪ Anticipating all the lonely hearts. ♪
♪ We all play parts on Friday night. ♪
♪ ‘Cause that's when the party starts! ♪
♪ And the party isn't over ‘til the bar runs dry, ♪
♪ and the next one too, where you catch my eye. ♪
♪ No the party isn't over ‘til we hail a cab and I go home with you. ♪
♪ See, the party isn't over ‘til I've seen your face. ♪
♪ And I know it's you, from outer space! ♪
♪ And the party isn't over ‘til I find the one. ♪
♪ 'Til I fall in love with you! ♪
Alright!
Well, it's four AM,and you know whatthat means, folks!
You're gonna finally playsome fucking Sondheim?
No, it means you have to gohome and don't forget to tip!
Mostly Sondheim my ass!
They should call it mostlyJason Robert Brown.
Goodnight everybody. Get home safe!
Goodnight!
You're ready to go?
I'm ready for a lot of things.
Hmm,I like the way that sounds.
Look!
The homosexual lifestyleis the biggest threatour nation has,
even more so than terrorism.
And they call themselvesChristians.
Didn't Jesus say
"Do to your neighbors as youwould have them do unto you"?
Well, that soundslike a good philosophy.
-Wait!-What?
No flood?No lightning?
No wrath of God?
I guess He approves.
C'mon.
We've gotta begood neighbors.
[Text signal]
Another text fromthe boyfriend?
Sebastian is not my boyfriend.
We've only been datinga couple weeks.
Honey, you've beensingle forever.
If I were you I'd callhim a boyfriend
just so I could say I hadone this millennium.
It's not about havinga boyfriend.
It's about findingthe right one.
I have a little surprisefor you.
Because you've bothbeen so wonderful,
I'm giving you somespecial wedding gifts.
What?! He's givingthem more stuff!
I bet they'll start singingshow tunes.
Art, fashion,creativity, music!
♪ Look at them who are so happy. ♪
♪ Look at them, so content. ♪
♪ Living there in our garden while we're here in a tent! ♪
♪ This fight isn't over. ♪
♪ No, they are gonna pay! ♪
♪ Those man who are so happy, ♪
♪ those men who are so gay! ♪
Maybe that's whatwe should call 'em.
Gays!
‘Cause they're happy.
Shut up!
Hey, this isn't my fault!
God and his damn fruit.
Oh, hey Steve.
Hey Adam.Look what I just made.
OK, now it's official.You are a genius!
Oh you're too sweet.
Who would've ever thoughtyou could get
this awesome juiceout of a potato?
Well look at these coolglasses you made.
-They're hand blown!-That has always been oneof your specialties.
What about last night?You figured out howto pull the skin back.
It's so much better that way.
I know, now I reallylike bananas.
Hey, I wonder if our kidsare going to be like us...
or like them.
What do you mean?
How do we now if our kids aregoing to be cultured and stuff?
Or like us?
Well, we'll just have toteach our kids to belike us, that's all.
And tell them to stay awayfrom the garden.
Hey!Who are you?
Hi, I'm Adam and thisis my husband Steve.
What's your name?
Cain.
Do you want a banana?
Mommy, can I eat Adam's banana?
Make sure you pullthe skin back.
Stay away from them!
They're trying to convertour children.
That's how they plan to do it.
They don't have to go throughlabor pains at all.
They just use fruit!
Cain!
God doesn't likethe gay people.
That's why he keeps them lockedup in the gated garden.
And He's given us...this entire desert,
which is why He loves us more.
♪ Be careful of gay people, ♪
♪ and their perverted needs. ♪
♪ They want you to be like them, ♪
♪ but God needs you to breed. ♪
♪ Those gays want to convert you ♪
♪ and your little brother too. ♪
♪ Make your parents proud of you. ♪
♪ You know just what to do. ♪
Go check onyour little brother.
♪ This fight isn't over. ♪
♪ No, they are gonna pay. ♪
♪ Those men who are so happy,♪
♪ those men who are so gay. ♪
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy!
What is it Cain?
I had to...I had to kill Abel.
What? Why?
He was...
He was singing a showtune.
NO!
Not a showtune!
♪ Somehow they got to Abel, ♪
♪ and taught him their sick ways. ♪
♪ Won't you please protect me Mommy ♪
♪ from turning out that way? ♪
Don't worry Cain. I'll protectyou from those people!
I promise you Mommy,I will never ever
sing a showtune.
♪ We'll show His chosen people ♪
♪ just who will win this fight. ♪
♪ Abel's death is on their heads now. ♪
♪ I know that we are right. ♪
♪ We must stop them from recruiting ♪
♪ new people to their fray. ♪
♪ And hate has many uses. ♪
♪ We hate those who are gay! ♪
Cain, get that book Mama'sbeen working on.
You mean the Breeder'sInformational Book ofLiving Examples?
Yes, honey.
But we call it the B.I.B.L.E.for short.
What are you writing it for?
I have to teach our descendantsto hate the gays.
Do you think this book willbe enough to warn themin the future?
What if they don't believe it?
They'll believe what they read.
In five thousand year from now,
they wont even know whowrote the damn thing!
♪ We'll get His chosen people. ♪
♪ Those men, we'll make them pay. ♪
♪ I will teach all of the children ♪
♪ to hate those who are gay. ♪
♪ All of those showtune singing ♪
♪ gays! ♪
Hey.
Hi.
You're cute.
Thanks.
I'm just here to relax.
I can help with that.
I'm actually seeing someone.
I'm not gonna tell him.
I'm not here to hook up.
C'mon,just let me suck you off.
No!
Just leave me the fuck alone.
I tried to be nice but Christ!
Dick.
Can I talk to you aboutsomething?
-Sure, what is it?-My parents are comingto opening night.
-That's great!-It is. I mean they've alwaysbeen so supportive,
but I never expected them tocome all the way for this.
It is your first New Yorkopening. You shouldn'tbe surprised.
I know, but my parentsare very religious.
Oh, so do your parents knowwhat the show is about?
I told them it was "Adam andEve - The Way God Made 'Em".
Yeah, there gonna be surprised.
And they don't knowabout me either.
This is gonna be good.
I'm sorry.
I'm serious.I'm freaking out.
They wouldn't let usread Harry Potter,
because it was all magicand against God.
Well if they think HarryPotter is sacrilegious,
I cant wait to hear theirreview of this show.
I try to be good, Idon't have sex...
But you've had sex right?
What?Seriously?
I wanted to wait forthe right guy.
But I don't really go out andmeet people so I neverreally found one.
Wow. But haven't youever been curious?
No.
Yes.I don't know. Look!
Sex is the last thingon my mind right now.What am I gonna do?
I wish I knew what to tell you.
My parents are gonna hate me.
No they're not.It's all gonna be OK.Trust me.
Look, we gotta go.We'll talk later?
Yeah.
Ok.
God I wish this wasn'thappening.
And just as the propheciesforetold, five thousandyears later,
God put Adam and Steveback on the Earth to provetheir love was real,
and able to beat the obstaclesof the modern world.
They were put indifferent places,
and in homes that used theBreeders Informational Bookof Living Examples.
♪ I was sitting backstage ♪
♪ and wondering what to say ♪
♪ so I raised my hands to Heaven ♪
♪ and I began to pray. ♪
♪ And Jesus said to ♪
♪ praise Him. ♪
♪ Jesus said to ♪
♪ love Him. ♪
♪ glorify Him. ♪
♪ Yes, Jesus said. ♪
♪ Oh, Jesus said ♪
♪ find salvation. ♪
♪ He said make a... donation. ♪
♪ Jesus said, oh Jesus said. Oh, yes he said! ♪
And Jesus said tome, "Patty Maye,
Patty Maye, I want you to goout and tell the peoplehow you feel.
Tell them how you feelabout being a Christian."
So Jesus, this one's for you.
♪ I'm proud to be a Christian ♪
♪ and to love my fellow man. ♪
♪ Proud to be a Christian ♪
♪ to help others when I can. ♪
♪ I'm proud to be a Christian ♪
♪ and be nice to everyone. ♪
♪ We're not better than the Jews or the Arabs ♪
♪ as they continue to fight. ♪
♪ We're not better than the Catholics, those boozers, ♪
♪ but we are always right. ♪
And do you know whyI know we're right?
♪ And Jesus said to ♪
♪ praise Him. ♪
♪ Jesus said to ♪
♪ love Him. ♪
♪ glorify Him. ♪
♪ Yes, Jesus said. ♪
♪ Oh, yes He said ♪
♪ find salvation. ♪
♪ He said make a... donation. ♪
♪ Jesus said, oh Jesus said, oh yes He said! ♪
Isn't she wonderful?
Everyday I thank the Lord forbringing me Patty Maye.
Now, do you knowwhat it is time for?
Well, I hope so.
It is time to hear about Jesus!
-Amen!-But before...
I can tell y'all aboutthe word of the Lord,
I need to talk to you aboutsomething very important.
My friends, partnersin my ministry,
we have fallen on hard times.
Now, we want to express acrossthe world our message,
but, we are runningout of money!
Now you know all themoney in your wallets
and in your bank accountsand on your credit cards,
well, that is not your money!
That is God's money,
and God needs his money back!
Hallelujah!
And then last thing, justat the end of "creation"
I want a sforzandoon the "aah",
so just watch me, it willbe like "aaaaahh!"
Like that, yeah?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Have a good second act.
Thank you.
So, what do you thinkI should do?
About what? Your parentsor your virginity?
What? Huh? What?You're a vir...
You'll have to excuse her.She's never had to usethat word before.
That is not true.I used to pray to Maryand she was a vir-
-Are you really a virgin?-This probably wasn't the bestplace for this conversation.
We can help you outwith your virginity.
Oh, no you can't.Leave him alone.
I didn't mean it like that.I meant come outwith us tonight.
We know a lot of hot boys.We can get you laid.
-Come out with us!-I'm not trying to get laid.
Going out tonight might begood for you. Take yourmind off things.
Give you a chance toclear your head.
And Sebastian and I will bethere to make surethese whores
don't put you on an expresstrain to hell.
Are you calling me a whore?
If I wasn't sitting in thischair right now, I'dtake my...
But you are, Blanche!You are!
To alcohol!
Go-go dancing. I couldn'timagine doing that.
Is he for real?Red panties.
I know, he has a zit onhis right butt cheek.
Alright, let's get him another.
-I'll be right back.-Okay.
Hey! Hey you!How you doing?
I've never been better.This was such a good idea.
Are you sure?You seem pretty wasted.
You can call it "wasted',I call it "free!"
Okay, just don't doanything stupid.
I'll show you guys dancing.
What is this?
No, no, no, no.
Alright, I am so overyou and your friends.
Oh my God.
So good!Don't knock yourself out.
I think this is yours.
I have no idea how itended up off of me.
May I help youput it back on?
You can help me do anything.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Not in front of my friends.
What?
We can't kiss in frontof my friends.
You know you kissed me right?
Yeah, I know, but
we can't do this infront of my friends.
Do you want to go somewhere?
I've always wantedto go to Paris.
Well, for tonight,lets go to my place.
That will do for now.
Hey hold this,I'll be right back.
Hey Eddie!
-Can I talk to you a minute?-Sure, what's up?
Are you sure you knowwhat you're doing?
Yeah, why?
I just want to make sure.
You and your newfound freedom.
You don't have to gohome with anyone.
Yeah I know.
I wanna go home with him.
He's really hot.
Okay.
I appreciate it.Goodnight.
-Be safe.-Uh huh.
I've never done this before.
Just relax.
Doesn't this feel good?
Yes.
Wait, shouldn't we get a con...
Don't worry about it.
Do you do this a lot?
No, you're special.
-So, what happenedto you last night?-What do you mean?
Well, first you were drunk, andthen you were with that guy...
-Scott?-Scott.
Did you do it?Did you tap his little ass?
Well, he actually...
-No!-What?
You bottomed for a bottom?
I don't even know whatto say to that.
-But you were safe, right?-What?
-You were safe, right?-Safe?
When you had sex, youused a condom?
He doesn't have sex a lot.He said it wouldhurt more if...
Are you serious?He's a slut!
Don't you ever haveunsafe sex again, you hear me?
Never! I don't carewho you're with.
You just met him, that's crazy!
-But he...-Never have unsafe sex!
Ok?
Yes.Fine.
Five minutes guys!
Thanks five.
So, what should I doabout my parents?
Well, whatever you do, don'ttell them a bottom bangedyou bareback.
I'm serious!
Look, whatever you do, whateveryou tell them, just...
make sure you do itbefore they get here.
[text signal]
What the hell?
What's wrong?
Someone told Sebastianthat I was HIV positive.
Oh, that makes sensenow, all the safe stuff.
-I'm so sorry, I didn't...-I'm not!
I'm not positive!
Benny, you know whatI think it's time for?
I think it's time to tell allour Christian friends
just what's going on in ourown family right now.
Are you sure you're upfor it, Sugar Plum?
I'm strong.
Strong.
For Jesus!
That's my Patty!
I'm not sure if y'allknow this or not,
but one of our very own singingangels is my nephew, Steven.
My sister became a Catholicfor her husband,
and they have beenraising Steven
as a Catholic!-Oh Lord.
Jesus just told me howmuch that hurt Him!
Now, a couple of weeks ago,Steven came to meand he said,
"Aunt Patty, I think there'ssomething you need to know."
Well, I clutched myheart and I said
"Please, dear Jesus. Let himtell me he's leaving theCatholic Church!"
Praise Jesus!
But no, he said, "Aunt Patty,
I am a hhh...homosexual."-Homosexual!
Well, I fell to my knees and Isaid, "No Jesus! No!He's become a priest!"
Oh no!
Well, thank Jesus, hewas not a priest.
But he was a hh...homosexual.
But at least that's a diseasewe can cure him of.
Well, Benny and Italked to him,
and we read him parts ofthe Bible where it sayshomosexuality is wrong.
God hates them.
Hates them!
And then, Jesus gaveme my mission.
And Benny and I togetherstarted a retreat program
to help those young homosexualson the straight path to Jesus!
-Good Lord!-To scare that demon ofhomosexuality out of them!
-Praise Jesus!-And we found a wonderfulrecovered homosexual
named Bruce Cohan,
not Cohen.
And he used to bea choreographeron the Broadway
until he found Jesus.-Yes indeed!
-And he will lead that retreat!-Yes Lord!
Now part of yourdonations today
will go towards the "FoundationAgainst Gayness Society."
Now, here's our nephew,the reformed Catholic,
and soon to bereformed homosexual,-Praise Lord!
Steven, to give his testimony.
-Praise Jesus.-Praise Jesus.
This whole situation has beenvery difficult for me.
You see,
I love the Lord,
but, I know He doesn't love me.
I know He doesn't wantme to be gay.
And I know He won't love meuntil I stop being this way.
♪ I will change for you. ♪
♪ I will change for you, my God! ♪
♪ I will be the boy you want me to be! ♪
♪ I will change for you. ♪
♪ I will change for you, my God. ♪
♪ I just want to know you love me again. ♪
♪ I'll cast off these wicked passions, ♪
♪ these desires that I feel. ♪
♪ I'll cast out these thoughts that so offend Thy will. ♪
♪ I will change, I promise, I will change. ♪
♪ I will change for you my God. ♪
Hey Sebastian, it's Paul.
Please call me back, weneed to talk about this.
I'm not positive. I don'tknow who told you that,but it's a lie.
Please call me back.Bye.
This is the Lyons. Leave a message and we'll call you right back.
Hi Mom and Dad, it's just me.
I just got out the show andI wanted to call to say hi.
Hope you guys are well.
We'll talk soon.
I love you.
A lot.
♪ Well, you know I've been a liar... ♪
I can't believe someonewould do that to you.
I mean, if someone told himI was a drunk or somethingI wouldn't care.
‘Cause it's true.
This is just vicious.
Fuck it.
I'll be right back.
That's Johnny, everyone!
All right, now it's time forus to bring up one of our
regulars here atMostly Sondheim.
Come on up, Dante!
He's not gonna singthat song again?
-Hey.-You better sing‘Meadowlark' later.
Ok.
This is one of myfavorite songs.
Oh yes he is.
♪ Fernando, the espresso man, ♪
♪ brings me java when he can. ♪
♪ I love him a lot a lot a ♪
♪ latte! ♪
Someone please shoot me!
Here.
Just shoot these.
♪ Fills my coffee with his cream! ♪
You're ok?
Yeah
♪ I love him a lot a lot a ♪
♪ latte! ♪
Thanks for coming here.
I just wish I wasin better spirits.-It's ok.
Is it strange that he'snot calling me back?
Who?Oh, thanks.
Scott.He isn't calling me back.
What'd you think wasgonna happen?
You met him. You had sex.That's pretty muchthe end of it.
But I thought he liked me.
Eddie, it's not about likingyou or not liking you.It was just sex!
-But it was so special.-It was just sex, trust me.
Just sex?So I should just go out andhave sex with people?
What the hell do I know?
Why does being gay haveto be this hard?
I don't know, but you can'tlet this get you down.
You can't let this asshole hurtyou. You just have to pick upand move on.
Everything is gonna be OK.
And if you're lookingfor more then sex,
you don't sleep with the guyan hour after you met him.
I just feel awful.
And my butt still hurts.
I'm sorry.
As Homer Simpson soadmirably put it,
"To alcohol, the cause of,and solution to,all of life's problems."
So, what are you gonnado about Sebastian?
Paul?
Yeah.
Hey!
Thanks for calling me back.
No, I'm fine.
I just have a lot on mymind right now.A lot!
Look, I can't really talkright now. I'm on myway to a dance class,
but I'll call you later.
Bye, love you.
Hey Sebastian, it's Paul.Again.
Listen, I just got tested foryou and I'm negative.
We need to talk.
What are you writing,your memoirs?
No, I'm just trying to getmy thoughts together.
You're OK?
Yeah, this whole Sebastianthing is just freaking me out.
Oh, I got tested.-And?
-I'm negative.-Of course.
But no matter how safe you are,those tests are just sonerve-wracking.
What did Sebastian say when youtold him you were tested?
Nothing. He hasn't evencalled me back yet.
He's an asshole.
No, he's just confused.
No, he's an asshole. You atleast deserve a phone call.
You know, I try and look fora healthy monogamousrelationship,
or someone to spendmy life with,
but I always end upgetting fucked.And not in a good way.
That's why I don't do thelove thing anymore.It get's too complicated.
What you need is toget fucked...and in a good way!
I want a husband, two pointfive kids, a house in theHamptons and a dog.
I don't wanna be a slutlike everyone else.
Are you talking about me?
Oh, I don't think the wordslut does you justice.
Bitch!
Whore!
Slut!
Oh, you wish!
Look, if you wanna change,then change.
If you don't, then stopbitching about it!
It's just sex, it doesn'thave to be special.
It's just like working out.But with someone else.
But I want sex to be special -to mean something.
But why?
Imagine if you wentto a theme parkand walked around
until you found the perfectrollercoaster.
By the time you pickedthe right one, the parkwould be closed,
and you wouldn't have gottento enjoy anything.
Sometimes you should justshut up and enjoy the ride.
Cute analogy.
I am impressed.
Thanks.
Go on.Be a slut.
Be a great big slut.Try ‘Manhunt.'
I'm not going on ‘Manhunt.'
Position?
Top.
Versatile.
Hello!
Tonight I've dug into my trunk
and pulled out a song that I'venever ever sung before.
It seems to be the newtheme song since I'vehad my ‘epiphany.'
♪ I was raised to have values. ♪
♪ Of my forbearance, my parents would be proud! ♪
This is fantastic!
♪ So forgive,this vulgar phrasewhich now I shall use. ♪
♪ God, I need to get plowed! ♪
♪ To hell with romance. ♪
♪ Just drop your pants. ♪
♪ I wanna be a slut. ♪
I decided to hook up online.
It's happening. The endof the world is upon us.
-Run for your lives!-Hell has frozen over.
♪ But now I don't care. ♪
♪ As long as my feet end up in the air. ♪
♪ Well, I wanna be a slut. ♪
I've tried the whole datingthing. It didn't work,so I'm trying something new.
-Show us your profile!-No!
Bitch, let us help you.We're professional sluts.Trust us.
♪ I'm eager to please. ♪
♪ I'm down on my knees. ♪
You're using your headshot?Child, I have a camera.
But do not use your headshot.That's just crazy!
♪ You'll be the grill, maybe I'll be the meat. ♪
♪ I'll be the harbor and you'll be the fleet. ♪
-Perfect!-But you cut off my head.
Exactly! Now we're gonnatake one with your face.
And you don't haveto show this pic
unless you're interested inthe guy you're talking to.
I never realized beinga slut was so hard.
♪ Like a teenage gorilla. ♪
Don't worry baby,we'll help you.
♪ You don't have to be all that buff or a jock boy. ♪
♪ Let's cut to the chase, ♪
♪ let's see your cock, boy. ♪
♪ All guilt has ceased. ♪
♪ Pretend I'm a priest. ♪
♪ I wanna be a slut! ♪
♪ In the john in the mall, ♪
♪ giving head in a stall. ♪
♪ I wanna be a slut. ♪
♪ Call me Maxwell, I'm good. ♪
♪ To the very last drop. ♪
♪ Call me bitch, call me whore, ♪
♪ go ahead, call a cop. ♪
♪ Whoever you call, just be sure he's a top. ♪
♪ I've tattooed a target on my butt. ♪
♪ Cause I wanna be a... ♪
It's like Will Rodgersalways used to say,
"I never met a manI didn't like."
♪ Cause I wanna be a slut! ♪
My parents woulda loved this.
Paul Connor everybody.
Lord! Take a break. Crazy!
Alright, let's dosomething else.
Sorry.
Hi.
Hey.
I really liked watching you.
Do you wanna see more?
Mm-hm.
You're place?
Sure.
♪ I met my love in a very odd way. ♪
♪ From a distance, we connected. ♪
That was awesome.
I do what I can.
Did you cum?
No.
Oh no, no.
I wanna make you cum.
I'm just really drunk.
Come on.
What?
Umm, yeah, uh,I don't cuddle.
Goodnight.
♪ Looking at men makes us sick! ♪
♪ We don't wanna suck on dick! ♪
♪ Sound off! -One, two. ♪
♪ Sound off! -Three, four. ♪
♪ Bring it on home. ♪
♪ One, two, three, four. ♪
♪ One, two. Three, four. ♪
Ok boys, it's time to starttalking about Jesus!
Sorry, I'm late.
Oh, that's OK Sweetie...
Son!
We're just gettingstarted here.
Steve, why don't youget him a T-shirt?
Thanks.
First thing I wanna do islearn our camp song.
And if you ever forgetwhat it's called,
all you have to do is look downon your camp T-shirt.
Now, this is how it goes.
♪ I'm gonna go straight... to Heaven. ♪
♪ I'm gonna go be Jesus' friend. ♪
♪ I'm never gonna be gay, be gay again. ♪
OK, now it's time forall of you to try.
♪ I'm gonna go straight... to Heaven. ♪
♪ I'm gonna go be Jesus' friend. ♪
♪ I'm never gonna be gay, be gay again. ♪
♪ Here at ‘FAGS' camp, we've come to learn ♪
♪ how to change our ways. ♪
♪ We're gonna stop being sissy men. ♪
♪ So when we pray to Jesus, we can say ♪
♪ I'm gonna go straight. Straight! ♪
♪ To Heaven. Yeah! ♪
♪ I'm gonna go be Jesus' friend. ♪
♪ Hey Jesus! ♪
♪ I'm gonna go straight... to Heaven. ♪
♪ I'm never gonna be gay, be gay again. ♪
♪ Here at ‘FAGS' camp, we're on our knees. ♪
♪ But it's just to pray! ♪
♪ We're gonna learn to be rugged and butch. ♪
♪ So when we pray to Jesus, we can say ♪
♪ I'm gonna go straight... to Heaven. ♪
♪ I'm gonna go be Jesus' friend. ♪
♪ We're never gonna be gay. ♪
♪ I'm gonna go straight... to Heaven. ♪
♪ I'm gonna go be Jesus' friend. ♪
♪ I'm never gonna be gay. ♪
♪ Be gay again. ♪
Excuse me! I saw the show.I just wanted to say hi.
-You saw the show?-Yeah.
There's no way you couldhave seen it and made itback here this fast.
Oh, well, I saw theshow last night,
but by the time I made itto the stage dooryou'd already left,
so I came to meet you tonight.
Glad you liked the show.
You look familiar.
Oh, I go to Mostly Sondheimonce in a while.
Oh, cool!Well, make sure you say hi nexttime you're at Sondheim.
Do you... think maybe we couldgrab a drink or go for coffeeor something?
I don't know. I have to runbut, I'm sure I'll runinto you again soon, OK?
Hey!
So, how was your workout?
Fine, yours?
It was good.
So I was thinking,
maybe we could...
-You know what wouldbe really hot?-What?
Not you.
Do you want to take a walk?
OK.
But don't try anything.
I won't touch you I promise.
It's so beautiful here.-I know.
Isn't it wonderful how God hasbrought us here to help us?
Help us?Help us what?
He should be helpingus break out.
Are you OK?Is there a problem?
-Am I doing something wrong?-Huh?
You haven't eventried to touch me.
-You just told me youdidn't want me to.-I thought you'd at least try.
I didn't take you here tomolest you. I just wantedto talk to you.
You're not even attractedto me, are you?
I think you're absolutelyadorable.
Then kiss me.
I want to know what its like.
You've neverbeen kissed before?
No.
Just kiss me, please.
-I can't!-Forget about the promise.
It's not about the promise.
It's about thisfucked up place.
-We should get back.-Why?
Are we just hangingout so we can make out?-No.
What else could we do?
Well, we could talk aboutthis sick place.
We can talk about who we reallyare. We can talk about...
Sick? This place is hereto help us becomewho God wants us to be.
Yeah. You go on andfind out who that is.
I'm already what Godwants me to be.
And where are you goingtonight mister?
My first online date.
Oh look,our little boy's gettingall dressed up for a trick.
It's like he's growing upright before our eyes.-Shut up!
I'd say good luck, butyou know these thingsare kind of a given.
-He's real hot too.-Yeah, if he sent youa real picture.
-What do you mean?-Don't listen to the bitter,dear. Just go have fun,
and give it to him onceor twice for me.
Goodnight boys.
Oh, thanks for the helpwith the profile.
That's what sluttyfriends are for.
Where are my pants?
Right here.
Thank you
Oh, hey!I guess we bumped intoeach other after all.
Hey!Nice to see you again.
Yeah, I gotta go to work.
Hopefully we bump intoeach other again.
Yeah sure.
Paul?
You look just likeyour picture.
I need a drink.
Cranberry vodka.-Alright.
You're really cute.
Thanks!I see you in here a lot.
I like the ambiance.
I bet you do.
I work down the block in theshow "Adam and Steve -
Just The Way God Made'Em."
I hear it's great.I'd love to see it.
I can get you comps. Giveme your number I'll callyou tomorrow and
hook it up.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Let me know when you wanna...
cum.
Yeah.
What are you doing after work?
Huh?
-The change is your tip.-Thank you.
I got a tip with yourname all over it.
Thanks.I'm already taken.
Come on!
Come home with me, I'll fuckyou like you've never beenfucked before.
Whoa Sparky, now you're gettinga little inappropriate.
Just give me another drink.
How about I give youa little water?
Why don't you just giveme a little vodka?
Why don't you go homeand sober up?
Why don't you just give meanother fucking drink?You know I know the owner.
Yeah, everyone knows the owner.
Just give me anotherfucking drink!
Are you fucking serious?
Go sober up.
Mom, Dad - I need totell you something.
So, how does thisusually start?
How do you want it to start?
This is all about you.
Umm...Well...
Would you like me toundress for you?
Sure.
So, tell me about yourself.
What would you like to know?
Where are you from?Why do you do this?
Well, I'm from Washington.Seattle, actually.
I go to NYU. And thisis how I pay for it.
Nothing crazy or anything.
Does your family knowyou do this?
No.They do know I'm gay though.
Are you seeing anyone?
Yes.
Does he know?
How would you like a massage?
Sure.
Isn't this whole thingstrange for you?
It was... at first.
And you probably end upsleeping with fat old men.
Sometimes I get to sleep withhot young guys like you.
Do you sleep with hotyoung guys a lot?
A lot of young guys justdon't wanna deal withdating or meeting anyone.
And with me there isno drama, you know?
No bitching, no nagging.And what you see iswhat you get.
I don't care if you wantme to top or...
if you want to fuckthe shit out of me.
Do you kiss all your clients?
Only the ones I want to.
Can I ask you a question?
You sure are full of questions.
I know this is strange but...
can I hold you?
I meant...
cuddle, hold you.
Sure.
♪ You don't have to be a millionaire ♪
♪ with a mansion full of art. ♪
♪ I just want someone to sing me a love song. ♪
♪ If you'd sing me a love song,♪
♪ a simple, tender love song, ♪
♪ you'd steal my heart. ♪
[CLUB MUSIC]
I didn't realize youwere working here.
I'm not having a good day.
You wanna talk?
Yeah.
Let's go downstairs.
What's wrong?
I told my parents.
-Did you tell them everything?-Yeah.
It didn't go well.
What did they say?
Nothing.
They always say they loveme and they said nothing.
I think my mom started crying.
I could almost hear theirdisappointment,
hear their hearts break.
They hate me.-They don't hate you.
It's tough for parentsto hear their kids aregay. It just takes time.
I can't imagine being anythingworse than gay.-Don't say that.
It's all going to beOK, you'll see.
No, it's not Paul.
You always say everything'sgoing to be OK, but it's not.
Sometimes its goingto be horrible.
Sometimes things turnout to be disasters.
You don't know what it's liketo have your parents hate you.
You don't know what it's liketo disappoint the peoplewho raised you,
and gave you everything.You don't know!
I just wish there was a cure.
Something I could taketo make me normal.
Some pill.Some shot.
You are normal Eddie. Why wouldyou wanna change who you are?
You know what, you shouldgo see that show,
"Adam and Steve - Just theWay God Made 'Em."
It might help you out.
Yeah, I hear the guy playingAdam is a slut.
I hear the guy who plays Stevejust popped his cherry.
Paul,don't you ever justwanna fit in?
No, I never try to fit in.
Could you imagine if I triedto be like the people Igrew up around?
I'd be watching professionalwrestling and drinkingbeer out of a can.
A can, Eddie!
For a date I'd buy anice box of wine,
drive to a parking lot tograb some girl's titties.
I don't mind being different.
I like it.
Because I know I'm better!
This is me.
Take it or leave it.
How is being a slutgoing for you?
Not too well.
I even hired a hustler.
Really?Was it good?
We cuddled.
You hired a hustler and youjust cuddled with him?
And you thought bottomingfor a bottom was pathetic.
I know, Eddie.
I'm just trying to figureout who I am.
And sometimes, wheneveryone around you
tells you you're supposedto be something else,
you start to think you are.
So you don't think youreally wanna be a slut?
I just wanna be loved.
Do you think my parentsstill love me?
What do you think?
You always make me feel better.
It is gonna be OK.
♪ The day I met you,♪
♪ I could hear the overture start ♪
♪ like a musical theatre love story ♪
♪ where a lover gives his heart. ♪
♪ I have never been in love. ♪
♪ This has got to be our gift from God above. ♪
♪ I won't change for you. ♪
♪ I won't become somebody else. ♪
♪ I am now the man I'm supposed to be. ♪
♪ I won't change for you. ♪
♪ I won't change for you my God. ♪
♪ I just want to know you love me as I am. ♪
♪ This is our musical theatre love story. ♪
♪ We're making it scene to scene. ♪
♪ Our love is strong and growing ♪
♪ on our journey to be free. ♪
-Hey Paul, can I askyou something?-Of course.
-I have a sore throat.-Take a cough drop.
No, I read online that it canbe one of the first signsof HIV and...
also my glands areswollen, and...
If you're scared you shouldgo get tested. It's free.
Do you think I might be?
After just once? I mean,wouldn't it be like asign from...
From what? God? Look,HIV is a disease.
It has nothing to do withGod or punishment.
If God wanted us dead, he'dsend down the fires ofSodom and Gomorrah.
Just go get tested.
Would you go with me?
Of course. But you'regonna owe me a drink.
And next time wrap it up.
God you're so stupid.
Alright everybody, we have a very special treat tonight.
We're about to pop somebody'scherry everybody.
We have a MostlySondheim virgin!
Come on up Charles!
Well, umm
I'd like to dedicate thissong to a special guy Ikeep bumping into.
I don't really know howto talk to him so...
I thought I would try talkingto him in his language- music.
So I wrote this for him.
♪ I have never believed in fate before, ♪
♪ but I'm seeing you most everyday. ♪
♪ You've been haunting my mind, ♪
♪ since I saw you in the light, ♪
♪ and you took my breath away. ♪
♪ There are forces at work ♪
♪ that we don't understand, ♪
♪ but they're bringing us closer ♪
♪ as if it were planned. ♪
♪ If someone up there wants us to be together, ♪
♪ then who are we to disagree? ♪
♪ If someone wiser knows we'd be good together, ♪
♪ it's not our place to ask why, ♪
♪ and I think we should give it a try. ♪
♪ If providence deems we fall in love, ♪
♪ then there's nothing we can do. ♪
♪ And I cannot deny what I'm feeling deep inside, ♪
♪ and I think you feel it too. ♪
♪ So it's hopeless to fight. ♪
♪ There's no place to retreat. ♪
♪ So give into your heart for surrender is sweet. ♪
Look, I should let youknow that I'm
really not looking to hookup or anything.
Me neither.
I just came out to my parentsand it didn't go very well
so the last thing onmy mind is sex.
I can't even imagine tellingmy parents I'm gay.
I'm Mormon.
Is that worse than beinga Southern Baptist?
♪ And I think we should give it a try. ♪
♪ I think we should give it a try. ♪
-How'd it go?-Good. I'm fine,
but they want me tocome back in a few monthsto do it again.
-OK.-Oh, I can't leave yet.
They want to take me back andgive me a counseling sessionin a few.
Teach me about safe sex.
No problem.I can wait.
Thank you so much forcoming with me.
I'm glad you're OK.
So...
I met a cute boy last night.
Oh, me too!
Mine sang me a song.
Mine's a Mormon.
I think we're both prettydamn pathetic.
I think I like being pathetic.
Eddie, you wanna come back now?
David?
I can't believe we'redoing this.
We said we weregoing to be here.
We can't miss the biggestopening night of his life.
Even if the whole showjust seems so wrong?
I am just as troubled by allof this as you are,
but he's still our son.
Hey everyone.
Now remember Patty has a newsong at the end of the show.
I can't believe they're addinga new song opening night.
They don't call it off-Broadwayfor nothing.
Ladies and gentlemen,welcome to opening night
of "Adam and Steve - Justthe Way God Made'Em!"
Before we begin, we mustinform you that thecoalition of Christians
has rated our show "FLAMING."
This doesn't mean we condoneor encourage thehomosexual lifestyle.
It just means that ifyou enjoy our show,
You'll end up burning inHell right next to us!
God? If you're listening,we need some help!
I'm frightened Adam,I'm frightened!
We're lost in the woods andwe don't know where we'resupposed to be going.
Hello!
Are you a good witchor a bad witch?
Why, I'm not a witch at all.
I'm your guardian angel,Dorothy.
An angel? Did God send youhere to bring us to Hell?
No Dear. He sent me here tobring you to New York City.
New York City is God'sfavorite city,
but you can't go thereshirtless. Here!
Wear these.
Aren't they a little small?
Trust me, Steve.It'll look divine!
These do look good.
You look great.
You too.
Did you think I wouldsteer you wrong?
After all, you're both friendsof Dorothy now.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course Steve.
Does God hate us becausewe're gay?
Honey, how could youeven think that?
♪ God made all different types of people ♪
♪ with different jobs to do. ♪
♪ He made all of the breeders ♪
♪ to make more gays like you and you. ♪
♪ So sure, they might be jealous. ♪
♪ Don't listen to what they say. ♪
♪ You're just the way he made you. ♪
♪ God loves gays. ♪
♪ Each one of you is special ♪
♪ in your own way. ♪
♪ Some people are gays in hiding. ♪
♪ They're the ones who love to shout. ♪
♪ They need to know God loves them ♪
♪ to help them with their coming out. ♪
God is going to send youto the fires of Hell!
♪ God loves gays, Honey. ♪
Being gay is an abomination,
and the only thing worse thanbeing an abomination...
is being a Jew.
♪ God loves gays, Mary. ♪
♪ God madly loves the gays. ♪
♪ God loves gays. ♪
♪ Yes he does. ♪
♪ Each one of you is special ♪
♪ in your own gay way, ♪
♪ and it doesn't matter ♪
♪ if you are butch or fey. ♪
♪ Stay just the way he made you. ♪
♪ God loves gays, Honey. ♪
♪ God loves gays, Mary. ♪
♪ No matter what your job is, ♪
♪ He loves you the way you are. ♪
♪ You can be a politician ♪
♪ or working in a leather bar. ♪
♪ God loves all He created ♪
♪ no matter what people say. ♪
♪ Stay just the way He made you ♪
♪ cause ♪
♪ He loves you. ♪
♪ He LOOOOO... ♪
♪ HE LOOOOVES...♪
♪ GAYS! ♪
I was up for that part.
I think I'm gonna like it here.
There are so many friendsof Dorothy here.
You know what this journeyhas taught me?-What?
That I want you inmy life forever.
Steve?
Will you marry me?
Of course I will.
No, no, no! You can't do this.This is an abomination.
The Lord God said that twomen should not sleep inthe same bed.
It is Adam and Eve,not Adam and Steve.
If God were here right now,what would He say?
Why don't you just ask me?
Who are you supposed to be?
What did they expect? God!
The Father.The man upstairs.
Watch this.
Let there be darkness.
I said LET THERE BE DARKNESS!
Now watch this -my favorite part.
Why the fuck is it sodark down here?
If you are God, then youknow it's Adam and Eve,not Adam and Steve.
You shouldn't believeeverything you read.
But your bookspecifically says...
My book? Who saidit was my book?
What do you think,I faxed it down here?
It was written by man.
It was interpreted by man.
It was abused by man.
I never told peopleto hurt and kill.
I told everyone to love.
You mean, you love the gays?
Didn't you just hearthe last song?
Maybe we were wrong.
I'm so sorry we triedto change you.
Can you ever forgive us?-Of course I can.
I love you both so much.
I guess we were wrong.
Forgive me
♪ I didn't realize ‘til now ♪
♪ that our cold, self-righteous words could hurt you so. ♪
♪ I was taught very young, ♪
♪ by those who came before me, ♪
♪ to fear and condemn ♪
♪ the things I don't know. ♪
♪ There is fear in the hearts ♪
♪ of those who would change you. ♪
♪ Fear of the light that shines from you. ♪
♪ They don't know that light was designed by God, ♪
♪ who gave it a brilliant and beautiful hue. ♪
♪ And to those who would change you, ♪
♪ or send you away, ♪
♪ you must proudly stand your ground and say, ♪
♪ I was put on this Earth as I am. ♪
♪ I was born with my own special blessings. ♪
♪ I let them shine and not give a damn. ♪
♪ I was put on this Earth as I am. ♪
♪ There is envy in those ♪
♪ who recklessly judge you, ♪
♪ wishing their hearts could love like yours. ♪
♪ They don't understand, they can reach within, ♪
♪ and find all the love, forgiveness restores. ♪
♪ And to those who condemn you with fury and shame, ♪
♪ you must strongly plant your feet and proclaim, ♪
♪ I was put on this Earth as I am. ♪
♪ I was put here to live as His creation, ♪
♪ and I know I'm loved in virtue and sin. ♪
♪ I'm calm and content within my own skin. ♪
♪ I was put on this Earth as I am. ♪
♪ I was born with my own special blessings. ♪
♪ I let them shine and not give a damn. ♪
♪ I was put on this Earth ♪
♪ as I am! ♪
Is there anything you wannasay to each other?
You know, marriage isa commitment of love.
It's the binding togetherof your two soulsthroughout eternity.
Don't ever make this commitmentunless you sure you're ready.
You know I love you,but are you ready?
If not, I'm willing to wait.
My whole life, I've wonderedwhat was wrong with me.
The problem was thatI hated myself.
And it made me feel so alone.
You will never be alone again.
You showed me howto love myself,
and now I'm ready to love you.
I'm so ready.
Our little Steven isgetting married.
♪ You'll never be alone. ♪
♪ I'll always be here for you. ♪
♪ I'll always love you, ♪
♪ and I'll be faithful to you. ♪
♪ Then with my blessing, ♪
♪ and as the angels sing with glee, ♪
♪ I'll call you one now ♪
♪ through all eternity. ♪
♪ You'll never be alone! ♪
I love you Adam.
I love you Steve.
And they're just theway I made'em!
That's our son!
Thanks.
We are so proud of you.